MARIAN BRUMA

Address: London, UK · Phone: 07796284625

Email: bruma.marian@yahoo.com · LinkedIn · GitHub · Portfolio

A hardworking, responsible, and eager-to-learn web developer with extensive experience working in the freelancing field, designing for a variety of clients.

Extensive knowledge of the main web languages - JavaScript, HTML, and CSS.

EXPERIENCE

MARCH 2020 - PRESENT

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

- Planning site designs, functionality, and navigation, along with audience funnels and data capture points.
- Building wireframes & prototypes in Figma or Adobe XD which were then turned into functional and responsive digital products.
- Reviewing UX and making necessary edits to accommodate technical or business concerns.
- Handling all composition, color, illustration, typography, and branding for projects.
- Creating landing pages using HTML5, CSS, JS, and specific brand logo in Adobe Photoshop.

MARCH 2019 - FEBRUARY 2020

F&B TEAM MEMBER, THE TOWER

- Manage all F&B and day-to-day operations within budgeted guidelines and to the highest standards.
- Lead F&B team by attracting, recruiting, training, and appraising talented personnel.

MARCH 2015 - FEBRUARY 2019

REGIONAL SALES MANAGER, S.C. MIFALCHIM GROUP S.R.L.

- Maintaining client records on a database.
- Coordinated stock inventory and requisition of new stock.
- Monitors competition by gathering current marketplace information on pricing, products, new products, delivery schedules, merchandising techniques.

JULY 2013 - FEBRUARY 2015

IT SUPPORT, S.C. TELECABLU S.R.L.

- Installing and configuring computer hardware, software, systems, networks, printers, and scanners.
- Provide basic remote end-user desktop support.
- Repairing and replacing equipment, as necessary.
- Possibly training more junior staff members.
- Troubleshooting LAN Networks & WIFI.
- Monitoring and maintaining computer systems and networks.

EDUCATION AND COURSES

SEPTEMBER 2019 – JUNE 2023

BSC COMPUTING TECHNOLOGIES, UNIVERSITY OF ROEHAMPTON

SEPTEMBER 2011 – JUNE 2015
ACCOUNTANCY, HIGH SCHOOL "EREMIA GRIGORESCU"

MAY 2021

DIGITAL MARKETING, GOOGLE DIGITAL GARAGE

CERTIFICATE ID: **Z2C ZEC 95P**

JANUARY 2021

LEARN TO CODE, UNIVERSITY OF LEEDS AND INSTITUTE OF CODING

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Java Script
- HTML/CSS
- Git/GitHub

- Responsive Design
- Bootstrap
- MySQL

MANAGERIAL SKILLS

- Front-End Development
- Client Relationship Management
- Management